// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Who is the father of C language?",
    answer: "1. Dennis Ritchie",
    options: [
     "1. Dennis Ritchie",
     "2. Rasmus Lerdorf",
     "3. James Gosling",
     "4. Stave Jobs"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which of these is NOT a relational or logical operator?",
    answer: "3. =",
    options: [
      "1. ==",
      "2. ||",
      "3. =",
      "4. !="
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "We can not use the keyword 'break' simply within ______.",
    answer: "2. if-else",
    options: [
      "1. while",
      "2. if-else",
      "3. for",
      "4. do-while"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "The global variables are ________.",
    answer: "2. External",
    options: [
      "1. Internal",
      "2. External",
      "3. Both Internal and External",
      "4. None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "The #include<stdio.h> is a ________.?",
    answer: "3. Preprocessor directive",
    options: [
      "1. Inclusive directive",
      "2. File inclusive directive",
      "3. Preprocessor directive",
      "4. None of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Out of the following snippet, which one will generate random numbers effectively?",
    answer: "2. rand();",
    options: [
      "1. rand(time(NULL));",
      "2. rand();",
      "3. rand(10);",
      "4. All of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "We can archive the modulus for float by: ",
    answer: "2. fmod(x,y);",
    options: [
      "1. x % y",
      "2. fmod(x,y);",
      "3. modulus(x,y);",
      "4. mod(x,y);"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "_______ tells a compiler that the data would be defined somewhere and it would be connected to the linker.",
    answer: "4. extern",
    options: [
      "1. variable",
      "2. yvals",
      "3. errno",
      "4. extern"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "The defination of the funtion abort() is in which header file?",
    answer: "1. stdlib.h",
    options: [
      "1. stdlib.h",
      "2. math.h",
      "3. stdio.h",
      "4. conio.h"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which of these properties of #define is false?",
    answer: "4. All of the above",
    options: [
      "1. These always obey the scope rules",
      "2. We can make use of a pointer to #define",
      "3. The #define can be externally available",
      "4. All of the above"
    ]
  },
];